so far we'VE looked at modeling systems, AH been that have discrete dynamics, as finite state machines, and hear the picture looks something like,
AH or whatever drawn here by the circles correspond to states, and all the arrows correspond to transitions between states, we also vary by,
we can look at modeling systems with continuous dynamics using a formalism such as ordinary differential equations, i'm sure of that the metal pictured,
you could have is that of the circles correspond to states of the continuous system which are points, in honour of a high dimensions,
but in an instant and dimensional space, AH various and determined by the number of a video booth, that or make up,
the state of the system so if you recall the helicopter example of , a if you think of the state of the helicopter is being on, the three location of the,
helicopters plus up the retrieval efficiency than you could think of and as being six very odd comprises x y z coordinates,
and then hot data exceed a y, as he does the east, okay, AH the rule your aunts and fitch,
of the helicopter, right and what we see here with this quickly a red line is is basically a cough, in armed,
AH in dimensional space that represents one possible evolution of the system state starting at some location that you see here,
and ending at some us some other point that you see here, he said so often in this particular lecture segment we're going to do,
pick up in a very quick peek, at a formal system that combines discrete and continuous dynamics, of these are called,