IT may look quiet but nigeria's in christ and the problems in this special stations across nigeria or clothes they simply don't have,
the petrol so people can fill up that caused transporting food is now a problem for much of the airline industry in nigeria is now grounded or,
or a few car going process, said the lucky ones, but there is another problem for this crisis or may, the problem with this crisis is on,
this be the generators run on diesel bought with no fuel available in the country as you can hear will not head the thought that running,
and use across nigeria because the national power grid supplies such as little electricity to its people , and its use will not just to run,
homes and businesses but banks and hospitals and many other key services to keep the country running, the court,
the nonresident no next we will pay , both lived on the top floor, the adult,
IT's difficult to imagine and understand quite what going on in nigeria right now but if you look on,
here IT is legal support, inside the port are disposed full of fuel is not a nigerian common imports the fuel problem if the governor,
subsidizes petrol and the fuel importers say that the bills on some states have been paid to stop distribution, and that means IT,
nigeria, is basically shutting down one example of, a simple example is a mobile phone said the famous black bear that was,
and on a generator that runs on diesel and foreign companies say they can be worthy of the continue running almost seven, everyone doesn't like cold, on,
along with this goes on in the world is gonna get, questions your voice and lagos nigeria,