the numbers tell a part of the story twelve hundred and fifty feet above the ground views stretching fifty miles on a clear day only,
a decade of rebuilding and once you ought to even on a cloudy day those numbers give way to feelings which are quite frankly difficult to describe,
we haven't won IT prestige can see the curvature of the aspen this point , that nature that you can feel the weight, of recent history, this construction of the,
building and the observatory, or a fish pond, for going forward for moving forward for saying, there is the future,
use and we embrace IT, k packets is the man in charge of the day to day running of the observatory architect t de go to dana helped design the structure,
south wing of its poles at two, in europe they are in is started you look down you can see the memorial if you have that sense of remembrance is not just about,
the views of the forty seven second elevator ride comes complete with a five hundred year time lapse of new york skyline, now you got a brief view of the world trade,
center on this side just for jobs, a moment and then IT disappears and then the view itself is revealed gradually aligned automatically,
beans, in a city crowded with skyscrapers one world trade center has serious competition, timely delivery and not the last year we have,
four point three million the empire state building's observatory broughton revenues of a hundred and eleven million last year a new, city is represented to some degree,
in the world, by the empire state building, few would dispute one world trade centre now shed that status, and with a predicted three point eight million villa,
IT is a year to the observatory IT could well match that success, for those involved in the projects serve IT already has, when i was five years old,
now you, he feels right, and they would have abandoned IT, and so out so that they do,
i think you don't have a very powerful feeling yes i do, i think they'll feel like this was the right thing, but about the indiana and new york,