on, the man murdered man in a,
on, our young man married a news share,
a, and, a, but,
eh, can you, a eh, a, on,
the, "]
on, a, on, the,
and, on, a, ma,
a, e,
and, i,
a, a, i,
and more than,
border, modern, was born,
i don't want to join a group morning and welcome to SAN francisco what you just saw that video was the opening of our life,
store in west like china is in han road china as IT is an incredible place in three gorges new design,
the architecture is amazing with other channel lever second floor is absolutely breathtaking, IT's the perfect place, to experiment,
our products' open bright is in accord with the great pain and this is the way we love to see your stores, AH,
with wonderful customers an amazing thing in the stores are really bad,
walk to life, they all are the heart and soul of our retail scene, now we are really proud to have the fantastic new home in china,
we'VE actually opened six stores in china in the last six weeks alone, we now have twenty one stored in china,
and we have a very aggressive plan to be at forty, by MID next year, we now have four hundred fifty three stores in fixing conference,
these are the best place to discover and explore products and world class support, and that's the reason, the over all hundred and twenty,
any million customers visited her stories last quarter, a law,
that's a very brief update on retell i am so incredibly proud, our retail team, a and on,
all the great things they do for customers, now we got a few more reason for your visit bookstores to die at the middle hop right and that,
i'm a sport with apple TV, now customers log to spring their favorite movie the favorite TV shows the photo of their,
to the big brain, we're offering content from all leading content providers and were adding more and more each day IT's probably noticed that your apple TV,
is there, now all the great channel that we have one apple TV there's one in particular i'd like to talk about this morning, in that its aged,
joe, a, we love h p l over the years they have,
created groundbreaking shows, IT really become a part of our culture and help shape our culture, shows like the products,
shows like entourage, inn of court, sex and the city, incoming next month on april twelfth,
IT's the return of eight, a, and silicon valley, end of course,
one of our favorites, the aim of, the day,
we'VE got the cie l a of h be a richer popular joining us is the friend of ours and he got some exciting news about h,
you have, are,
thank you to have good morning everyone on behalf of all of us age be out, let me return your compliment by saying that when you love apple,
in all the extraordinary products, which capture the imagination of many people all over the,