david cameron evoked the spirits of winston churchill as he embarked on his great european champaign the prime minister was entertaining strong cold humid,
the european commission president whose appointment he tried to block last year to deter attackers and only agenda some tough talking with,
cameron say mom's for a better deal for britain ahead of IT out referendum or the next year or the year of the, dinner with MR young to have,
the checkers is the first part of a charm offensive which will take MR cameron is ture of many european capitals over the next few weeks, is aimed to pursue,
why do you lead us to bracket involves the renegotiation of the terms of britain's membership of the u, but MR cameron who admitted to some,
within latvia last week that he's tough would be easy has already angered political opponents by borrowing from voting at one point five,
the europeans who lived here in the u k even though they can vote in european and local elections, people like me and i have been released,
really think you have bats, givenchy local identity and to have a house here i want to stay here, man in my opinion i think we should advance the,
and , i have permission was more customers, parents are often harms the effect of movies about families saved,
oh please, however me, everything round of the communication by paul to also communicate, however norms, for the second,
fields also be foreigners, a, a, what does the camera has also declared that succeed in seventeen year old voted on,
scottish referendum on independence last september should not take part either, i love you say that the patients entered on engaging part expresses,
and the turnout for the referendum to prove that we do cast and having a voice should be high to feed back the attacking creature able to know your definite,
draw still or deviated saw no more than a century the adults of the future i think we should have a say in what can happen for our country in a major youth senses the general,
election labour now supports a referendum vote will attempt to amend the eu referendum bill sikes sixteen and seventeen year olds,
invites you to join the armed forces could marry you can stop work to pay taxes, i think teaching is the general should also be able to take part in this hugely important decision,
students can affect their future as well as everybody elses, sat out in the scottish referendum was a massive eighty five percent of , the u,
cole is unlikely to match that when ever IT's held, jon craig sky news checkers,